<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mhdy.com</title>
    <link>https://mhdy.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mhdy.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://mhdy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://mhdy.com/privacy_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhdy.com/privacy_policy/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t like cookies? Use your browser to block them. My site doesn&amp;rsquo;t collect or store any private data by default. I do use 3rd party analytics software such as Google Analytics which is common online. For more information on Google Analytics and their cookie policies, be sure to look it up online.
Technology Used  Google Analytics  Email Forms If you use the contact form, keep in mind:
 Don&amp;rsquo;t send sensitive information, the submission is routed through 3rd party email providers before it ends up in my regular inbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility Statement</title>
      <link>https://mhdy.com/accessibility_statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhdy.com/accessibility_statement/</guid>
      <description>Accessibility Statement MHDY.com is committed to providing a website that is accessible to the widest possible audience, regardless of technology or ability. I am actively working to increase the accessibility and usability of this website and in doing so adhere to many of the available standards and guidelines.
This website endeavours to conform to WCAG 2.1 AA; or level Double-A of the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) Web Content Accessibility Guidelines 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a fast and lightweight website</title>
      <link>https://mhdy.com/building_a_fast_and_lightweight_website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mhdy.com/building_a_fast_and_lightweight_website/</guid>
      <description>It was time to redesign my website, and I needed to move from a static image website (used to showcase the occasional photograph I took) to one that supports UX and CRO focused articles. My journey involved learning the HUGO Static Site Generator to produce a fast and lightweight website, leveraging CSS Grid to create a code optimized responsive design, all while achieving the ever elusive Google Page Speed score of 100%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
